Guide to the Sam Reiss Photographs PHOTOS.021.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Unions., 1950-1975
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Convention - Miami, Florida - (color), circa 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Convention - Miami, Florida - Proofs - (Folder 1 of 4), circa 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Convention - Miami, Florida - Proofs - (Folder 2 of 4), circa 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Convention - Miami, Florida - Proofs - (Folder 3 of 4), circa 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Convention - Miami, Florida - Proofs - (Folder 4 of 4), circa 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Convention - Unidentified, circa 1970's (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Laundry Workers Division, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Laundry Workers Division - Jullisi Day Care Center Project, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Laundry Workers Division - Retirees, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Meeting With Kovenetsky and Howard Samuel, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - New York Joint Board Headquarters, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Retirees, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards, 1950-1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Sidney Hillman Health Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Summer School, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Unidentified Meetings And Social Gatherings, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Union Industries Information Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Wholesale Clothing Clerks Union, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Amalgamated Industrial Union, Local 76B - Award To John Ansonia, circa 1971 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - American Federation of Musicians, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, District Council 37, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - American Federation of Teachers [?] - Unidentified Meeting (including attendees [representatives?] from Asia, Africa and possibly Latin America); Albert Shanker leading (?), undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Communication Workers of America, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Federation of Catholic Teachers, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - Local 3 - Art Show, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - Local 3 - Bayberry Land Retreat, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - Local 3 - Circus, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - Local 3 - Education Conference - Wagner College, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - Local 3 - Plaque Presented By Canadian First District Local Union In Commemoration Of Joint Seminar At Bayberry Land - (color), Sep 1972 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - Local 3 - Unidentified Meetings And Social Gatherings, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, District 9, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters [?], Local 815 - Members Or Officers [?], undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, Local 62, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, Local 600-601 (Puerto Rican Local), undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union - 75th Anniversary Event, Jun 1975 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - International Longshoreman's Association, Local 1814, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - International Union of Dolls, Toys, Playthings, Novelties and Allied Products (USA/Canada), undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 431, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 463, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 463 - Voting, Feb 1972 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Ironworkers International Union, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Laborers International Union of North America, Laborers Local 147 (Sandhogs), undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Retail Clerks International Association, Local 888, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Retail Wholesale and Department Store Workers Union - Limit Imports, Save Jobs Campaign, undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Retail Wholesale and Department Store Workers Union, Local 1-S, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Retail Wholesale and Department Store Workers Union, Local 338, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Retail Wholesale and Department Store Workers Union, Local 1125 - Stewards Training, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Retail Wholesale and Department Store Workers Union - Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Service Employees International Union, Local 144 - Gonzales, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Sheet Metal Workers' International Association - Dinner, Americana Hotel, undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Textile Workers Union of America, Mar 1975 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Transport Workers Union - Constitutional Convention - Miami, Florida, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Transport Workers Union, Local 101, Mar 30, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Transport Workers Union, Local 504 - Air Transport Division - Hewitt Hall Dedication, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Transport Workers Union, Local 504 - Air Transport Division - Swearing-In, Apr 1975 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Transport Workers Union, Local 1400, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Transport Workers Union, Local 3036, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Transport Workers Union - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Transport Workers Union - Porters, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Transport Workers Union - Retirement Celebrations, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 - Dental Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 - Retirees, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - United Automobile Workers of America, Local 259, undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - United Farm Workers of America - "El Paso", undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - United Farm Workers of America, Local 140 - Baseball Team, undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - United Federation of Teachers - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - United Federation of Teachers - National Education Association - Merger, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - United Federation of Teachers - Spring Conference, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - United Furniture Workers of America, undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - United Furniture Workers of America, Bedding Curtain and Drapery Workers, Local 140, undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Series II: Labor Organizations., 1951-1975
  - AFL-CIO - Convention, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO - Merger Convention, New York City, Dec 1955 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO (?) - National Institute of Health Awards presented to Mary Lasker and George Meany (Lane Kirkland accepting for Meany) - New York City, circa 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO, New York State - 14th Annual Constitutional Convention, Hilton Hotel - Rockefeller Center, New York City, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - AFL-CIO, New York State - 15th Annual Constitutional Convention, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO, New York State - 16th Annual Constitutional Convention, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
  - AFL-CIO, New York State - 17th Annual Constitutional Convention, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - AFL-CIO, New York State - Ray Corbett, President New York State AFL-CIO, Made Honorary Mohawk Chief, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - AFL- CIO - Unidentified gathering [includes Hugh Carey, George Meany Lane Kirkland, Jacob Potofsky, Murray Finley, Albert Shankar, Ray Corbett, Murray Finley], Jan 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Allied Union Social Club of Quebec - Give To The Irish Relief Fund Campaign, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Black Trade Unionists Committee - A. Philip Randolph Honored, City Hall, New York City, Oct 19, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Black Trade Unionists Committee, New York City Central Labor Council, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Black Trade Unionists Committee, New York City Central Labor Council - Albert Shanker, Doris Turner, Edward Welsh honored by Department of Labor, Jun 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Black Trade Unionists Committee, New York City Central Labor Council - Matthew Guinan and Carole Graves Honored, Jun 2, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Building Trades Meeting, Apr 19, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Canadian Labor Congress, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - CIO - 13th Constitutional Convention, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - CIO - 17th Constitutional Convention, Dec 1, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - COPE - Meeting in Support of Burke-Hartke Bill [including Senator Clifford Case], 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21-22)
  - Electrical Industry, Education And Cultural Fund - Awards Dinner, Apr 15, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Electrical Welfare Club, Inc., undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Hispanic Labor Committee, New York City Central Labor Council - Honors D. Siegal and L.L. Levine, Jan 6, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Histadrut -- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Histadrut - Honors Yitzhak Rabin, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Labor Committee - Honors Harry Van Arsdale, undated (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
  - Jewish Labor Committee - Honors Lane Kirkland, Nov 28, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Joint Industry Board of the Electrical Industry, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - League for Industrial Democracy, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - League for Industrial Democracy - Dinner Honoring Frederick O'Neal, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - League for Industrial Democracy - Honoring George Meany, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - League for Industrial Democracy - Honoring Henry Jackson, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - League for Industrial Democracy - United Steel Workers, [Local?] 903, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - National Religion and Labor Foundation, Dec 14, 1955 (?) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - New York City Catholic Council of Electrical Workers, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Annual Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Annual Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 19-20)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Annual Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 21-22)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Annual Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 23-24)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Annual Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Civil Rights Conference, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Committee on Civil Rights, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Community Services, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Unidentified Meetings and Events (Folder 1 of 3), undated (Box 14, Folder 6-8)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Unidentified Social Gathering [including Bayard Rustin and William Bowe], undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - New York City Central Labor Council - Unidentified Social Gathering [including officers from the United Federation of Teachers], undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - New York City Central Labor Council [?] - International Delegation To, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - New York City Central Labor Council [?] - Japanese [Labor Union?] Delegation Visits Dental X-Ray Facilities, ndated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - New York Labor-Management Council Of Health And Welfare Plans, Inc. - Conference On National Health Insurance, Jul 29, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Union Label And Service Trades Council Of Greater New York And Long Island, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Union Label Trades And Services Council Of Greater New York And Long Island - Annual New York State Labor-Management Show, Date Unknown (color prints), undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Union Label And Service Trades Council Of Greater New York And Long Island - Little Miss Union Maid, National Poster Child, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - United Italian American Labor Council, Inc., undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Series III: Demonstrations/Rallies/Parades., 1957-1975
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Action Against Alexander's [Department Stores], undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Demonstrations, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Demonstration Against Imported Clothing, Nov 1974 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Farah Strike, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Farah Strike - A & S [Department Store] Boycott Picket Line, circa 1973 (Box 14, Folder 22-23)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Farah Strike - Korvette's [Department Store] Picket Line, circa 1973 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Farah Strike - Macy's [Department Store] Picket Line, circa 1973 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Farah Strike - Related Miscellaneous, circa 1973 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Farah Women, circa 1973 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Political Action, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Pro-Stevenson Union Rally At Union Square With President Harry Truman, undated (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Strike, Jun 1974 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists - Protests At ABC Over Overseas Bicentennial TV And Film Productions, New York City, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Building Construction and Trades Council (?) - (A Hard Hat Demonstration?) - Peter Brennan With Uniformed Soldiers And Sailor Wearing Construction Helmets, circa 1970's (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Building Services Employees International Union, Local 32- E - At United Federation of Teachers Demonstration, undated (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Building Trades Demonstration, Dec 1974 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Communication Workers of America - Local 1101 Strike, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Communication Workers of America - Local 1177 Against Western Union, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Demonstrations - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Demonstrations - Unidentified, undated (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Dining Room Employees Union, Local 1 - Picket, undated (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Earth Day, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Electrical/Gas Rate Hikes - Protest Against, undated (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Free Soviet Jews Demonstration [includes Hubert Humphrey & Hugh Carey], Apr 1975 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Funeral Procession(s) for Martin Luther King, Jr. (Atlanta and Memphis) - Prints and Contact Sheets, Apr 1968 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Golden Ring Council of Senior Citizens - Salute to Wilbur D. Mills - Town Hall, New York City, undated (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3 - Demonstrations (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 804 - Strike Against United Parcel Service, Oct-Nov 1974 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 810 - New York University Maintenance Workers, undated (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union - Anti-Segregation Protest Against Bus Companies, undated (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union at Jobs Rally, Washington, D.C., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, Local 483 - Strike Against Fedders, undated (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 891 - At United Federation of Teachers Demonstration, undated (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - International Union of Painters and Allied Trades, District Council #9, undated (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - International Union of Painters and Allied Trades, District Council #9 At United Federation of Teachers Demonstration, undated (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Jewish Labor Committee - Rally In Support Of Jackson Amendment, Ca. 1974, circa 1974 (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Labor Day Parades, undated (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Labor Mass At St. Patrick's Cathedral, New York City, Sep 11, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Local 1199 - (New York) City Hall Demonstration, undated (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Strike, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - New York State Law Enforcement Union, Council 82 - At AFSCME - Demonstration Against Rockefeller Cutbacks, undated (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 153 - Strike Against Macmillan, undated (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, Local 3 - Teachers' Strike, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - Picket Line For Boycott Against FINAST Grocery Store[s?], undated (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Professional Staff Congress And United Federation of Teachers, Local 1460, undated (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Pro-Israel Demonstration, undated (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Protest Against Atomic Weapons - Early 1960's (?), circa 1960's (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Protest Against Killings of Iraqi Jews Demonstration In Front of Iraqi Mission To the United Nations, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, Local 1-S - Strike Against Macy's, undated (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, Local 3 - Strike Against Macy's, Apr 1972 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, Local 3, United Store Workers Union, undated (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Service Employees International Union - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Service Employees International Union, Local 1199 - Demonstrations, undated (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Soviet Mission Picket, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Stevenson, Adlai -- Rally, circa 1949-1965 (Box Shared Tamiment 200, Folder 4)
  - Textile Workers Union of America - Textile Oneita Strike, Demonstration In New York City, In Support Of, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Transport Workers Union, undated (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Transport Workers Union - Last Day Negotiations, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Transport Workers Union - New York City Subway Strike, City Hall, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Transport Workers Union - Participation in Martin Luther King, Jr. Funeral Procession(s?) - (Atlanta and/or Memphis), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Transport Workers Union - Preparation For Torchlight Parade, 116th Street, Transport Workers Union Supports Humphrey/Muskie, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Transport Workers Union, Air Transport Division - Pan American Airlines Strike, undated (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Transport Workers Union, Taxi Drivers Local 3036 - Strike, 1965; And Funeral For B. Rivera, 1970, 1965, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Transport Workers Union, Utility Division, Local 101, undated (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Council Of Greater New York And Long Island - Labor Day Parade - Miss Union Label, undated (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Union Protest On Behalf Of Jailed Newark Teachers, North Caldwell, New Jersey, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - United Farm Workers - At Cathedral Of St. John the Divine, New York City, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - United Farm Workers - At Union Square, New York City, May 1975 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - United Farm Workers - Cesar Chavez Protests U.S. Government Buying Scab Grapes At Fort Hamilton Army Base, Brooklyn, New York, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - United Farm Workers - New York City Labor Unions Support United Farm Workers/Cesar Chavez, undated (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - United Farm Workers - Picket At Grand Union [grocery store] In Support Of Grape Boycott, 1970's (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - United Farm Workers - Rally [including Cesar Chavez, New York City Mayor John Lindsay and various union officials], undated (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - United Federation of Catholic Teachers - St. John's University Strike, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - United Federation of Teachers - Demonstrations, undated (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - United Furniture Workers of America, Local 140 - La-Z-Boy Strike - Ca. 1960's (Box 3, Folder 219)
- Series IV: Personalities/Portraits., 1930s-1975
  - Abel, I.W., Mar 1975 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Abramson, Irving - At Celebration Honoring Him (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Adelstein, Bernard - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 813 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Allen, Fred (Comedian), circa 1940's (?) (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Arcuri, Andrew (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Armstrong, Louis (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Avrutin, Harry (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Bacchieri, George - (United Furniture Workers of America) Receives State Of Israel Bonds Award, Jan 31, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Bahr, Morton - (Communication Workers of America) Presentation Of B'nai B'rith Youth Services Award, May 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Barlogh, Ed - Madison Square Garden, Jun 1974 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Beck, Burt - Union Official And Newspaper Editor, Jun 1974 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Beichman, Arnold (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Bierne, Joseph A. - Communications Workers of America (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Biller, Moe - American Postal Workers Union (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Bowe, William H. (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Brand, Morris, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Brennan, Peter (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Burnell, John T. (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Cabell, Connie - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Capra, Peter (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Carey, Hugh (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Chavez, Cesar, 1960's (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Chisolm, Shirley (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - Clark, Ramsey, 1960's (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Clayman, Jacob - Eugene V. Debs Award, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - Colasanto, Frank (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Communication Workers of America - Installation Of Officers (xerox copy) (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - Corbett, Ray (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Costigan, Tom (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - Cranston, Monroe - St. Joseph's A.O. Church (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Curran, Joseph H. - International Association of Machinests and Aerospace Workers, Feb 26, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Daniels, Wilbur - International Ladies Garment Workers Union (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Dayan, Moshe and Lane Kirkland, Nov 1974 (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Dee, Ruby and Ossie Davis, Jun 1975 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - DePolo, Agnes - President Of The Candy And Confection Workers Union, Local Jo 23-03-45, 1A Road, L.I.C., NY (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Donahue, Thomas R. - Service Employees International Union, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Dubinsky, David (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Eban, Abba - Dinner With Jacob Potofsky And Various Other Union Officials (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Eiger, Milton (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Feldman, Ben - President, International Leather Goods Union (Box 3, Folder 259)